People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning, Church!
My name is Hezron Konlan.
The gentleman beside me is Laar Joshua. He is my closest friend.
People of God, I am here to share my experience of my encounter the first time I came to The SCOAN.
I saw an angel, people of God!
As am speaking, I believe they are here in our midst.
You all should believe that the problems you carried to the church would be dropped here.
It doesn't matter whether you are touched or not.
Believe it.
The man of God said something which I believed.
He said that you don't have to wait until you are touched by him.
Your problem is known; once you are here, you are free.
Once you are here, your past is over.
As he said that, my faith was lifted up.
I believed in what he said because I had watched him and I know who he is.
Throughout that day, I meditated on that message and prayed over it.
I was here with my problem but I couldn't enter the church.
I sat at the overflow congregation, outside here.
At the end of the church service that day, we all went home.
The following day, I was in a bus opposite the main entrance of The SCOAN -
there is a car station just opposite the entrance -
waiting for the driver and other people to load the goods in the car.
Then, I was a bit curious and said, "God, I know You are here,
I know You have touched me, I know I am blessed.
But I need an evidence, show me an evidence that The SCOAN is a real place, you are present here
and Prophet T.B. Joshua is a real man of God.
I need an evidence - reveal to me that you are here".
After saying that, I got a direction to take my phone and turn on the video.
I turned on the video and started videotaping.
I didn't know what I was videoing because I was not videoing any specific object.
I just had the direction that I would see evidence.
So, I started videoing.
In doing that, all of a sudden, I saw an angel dressed in a white gown,
seated on a huge animal which I would say is like a horse.
It was very huge.
The angel crossed from the other side of the road and then entered the main church.
I was with my friend here. I turned to him and said, "Charlie, I have seen something.
Charlie, I saw an angel and it was real, physical".
Then, I opened the video and showed him.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
People of God, at this point, we want you to watch the screen of your television.
We are going to show you the very clip that our brother captured on his phone,
that day he came to The SCOAN.
Let's watch the screen of our television right now and see what happened.
He is the very brother who took this video in question and he is here to share this experience.
Let's watch our screen.
Charlie, I saw something.
This one - physical.
Charlie, I saw something physically.
It went into the Church.
Viewers and those present here, the reason we are bringing this to your attention is that
several months ago, in early January 2018, this clip was discovered on the internet and
as many of you may have known, the clip subsequently went viral,
was shared around the world and viewed thousands of times.
We did not actually know the person that took this video footage.
We had no knowledge of this gentleman that took this footage.
We were actually looking for the person concerned
so that he would be able to come and tell us what he saw that day.
To the glory of God, after this footage went viral on the internet,
our brother from Ghana came forward and said he was the one
and even showed us the original footage that he took on his phone that day,
concerning this clip that we have watched.
Once again, this is the reason we are bringing it to your attention
so that he can be in the position to explain himself, what he saw that day,
the prayer he offered, and the reason he was actually holding a phone to take a video
outside of The SCOAN and this incident was captured to the glory of God.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Finally, brother, what is your advice to people around the world, after this encounter with Jesus?
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My advice to those who are watching me here and those viewing me on television is that
all you need to do is to believe, distance is not a barrier as Prophet T.B. Joshua always says.
Since that encounter, my life has never been the same again.
I didn't meet Prophet T.B. Joshua, he didn't touch me, and I didn't even enter the church.
But my life changed.
I have been moved from where I was to a different person today.
So, believe in the existence of God at The SCOAN,
angels are present here, they are touching everyone.
Release your problems to them and you will be free.
Thank you.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
I am Joshua Laar from Ghana.
The man beside me is my closest friend.
If there was another word to use, I wouldn't have used the word 'friend'.
He's beyond a friend.
Like he rightly said, on that faithful day when we came, I was inside the bus with him.
When he was videoing, I was there.
I was there, I saw whatever happened.
After videoing it, he showed it to me.
When I saw it, it served as a motivator to me.
What he said to me was that, "Jo, look at this". Then, he showed it me.
When I saw it, I said, "Ah, let me see it again!"
I wanted to know what it was. I watched and paused, and then I realised that it was an angel.
It was then that he said to me that, "Joshua, we have a living God".
Since then, we have been planning to come to The SCOAN and give a testimony.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!